# KOMAL POTE

# UX / UI Designer and Developer

Mumbai, India, 400084 | +91 9920564656 | komalpotey@gmail.com

# Summary

I have more than several years of experience in developing web application using HTML, CSS, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Bootstrap. Worked on different project based companies as a web designer or developer. I am having good knowledge in SEO and basic level of JavaScript and jQuery. So i can work with full dedication and honesty with my clients. My aim is to give the best output and provide 100% satisfactory outputs to client

## Experience

Sr. UI Developer Feb 2023 To Current

## Ruloans Distribution Services Pvt Ltd - Mumbai, Maharashtra

- 1. Developing responsive HTML Emailer clean design
- 2. Develooing Responsive clean UI design with the React-Bootstrap webpages
- 3. Created HTML marketing email templates for: Mailmodo, Sendy, Corefactors
- 4. Running email marketing campaigns end to end

Sr. UI Developer Dec 2020 to Jan 2023

#### Digitel Design Studio - Mumbai, Maharashtra

- 1. 3.8 years of demonstrated experience in creating and implementing UI development
- 2. Detailed experience with coding and the ability to troubleshoot and analyze websites using HTML, CSS and comparable languages
- 3. Ability to prioritize and manage multiple milestones and projects efficiently
- 4. Ability to work effectively in a collaborative environment to create top-performing interfaces
- 5. Created responsive web layout with following SEO Guide line.
- 6. Proficient with visual design programs such as Adobe Photoshop

May 2019 to Nov 2020 **UX / UI Designer and Developer** River Route Creative Group LLP - Mumbai, Maharashtra

- 1. Experienced Frontend Developer Converted PSD file into html
- 2. Working on more than 10+ Project Website UI / UX Design
- 3. Good understanding of SEO
- 4. Skilled in Front-end Development, Bootstrap, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), Database, sql and PHP.

### Skills

UI Development

User Experience Design

Adobe Photoshop

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

Creativity

React Js

Hard work

Communication

#### Basic

HTML

JavaScript

**JQuery** 

sql

### Education

2022 FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT

1<sup>st</sup> Class Sith Computer Institute, Ghatkopar

2018 DIPLOMA IN UX / UI DESIGN

1<sup>st</sup> Class Edit Institute, Dadar

2016 BACHELOR OF COMMERCE (B.COM)

C Grade Mumbai University